Drew Holbrook

Profile

I'm a software engineer based in Crested Butte, Colorado. I'm the co-creator of Ekko, a self deployable realtime infrastructure with in-transit message processing that was built with a team of fully remote software engineers. I have multiple years of experience with the Ruby and Javascript ecosystems and am comfortable with AWS and Docker.

Skills

Backend	Frontend	Tooling	Cloud
Node.js, Express, Ruby,	JavaScript (ES6)	Git/GitHub, Docker, Linux	AWS, Digital Ocean,
Go, PostgreSQL, SQL,	React/Redux		Heroku
MongoDB, RESTful APIs	HTML/CSS		

Professional Experience

2021 – present	Co-Creator, Software Engineer
----------------	-------------------------------

Ekko 🛮

- Co-created Ekko, a self deployable realtime infrastructure with in-transit message processing
- Built websocket server using Node.js, socket.io, and Redis
- Designed AWS infrastructure (Application Load Balancer, ECS Farget, S3, Elasticache, Lambda)
- Automated infrastructure deployment with AWS Cloud Development Kit
- Built CLI tool for infrastructure deployment, teardown, and Lambda management
- Load tested the real-time service using artillery.io to simulate 50,000 concurrent connections
- Collaborated daily with a team of fully remote engineers
- Co-authored Ekko's case study: https://ekko-realtime.com/

2018 – 2021 Full-Stack Web Developer

Self Employed

- Yello: Trello-like app with React/Redux font-end, Node.js, Express, MongoDB REST API backend
- Airline Routes: React app bootstrapped with Create React App

2015 – 2018 Director of Marketing and Development

Crested Butte Nordic ☑

• Helped grow revenue by 230% over three years

2014 – 2015 Director of Events

Crested Butte Nordic 🛮

• Managed over 100 volunteers and organized events for more than 1000 participants

Education

2004 – 2008 **B.A. Economics**

University of Vermont ☑